# JACKSON **HAGOOD**

### Computer Engineering Student & Future Software Engineer

# **Profile**

Senior Engineering student at Texas A&M University with a 4.0 GPA. Worked as Software Engineering Intern at JPMorgan Chase in Summer 2022. Currently work as a teaching assistant in the CSE department at Texas A&M. Will be returning to JPMorgan Chase next Summer as a Software Engineer (SEP) in Plano, TX.

# Education

### BS Texas A&M University 8/2019—Present

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering (Computer Science track, CECN)
- Minor in Mathematics
- 4.0 GPA, 116 hours completed (senior classification)
- Dean's Honor Roll
- Member of Tau Beta Pi (Texas Delta Chapter)
- Expected graduation May 2023

# Work Experience

#### Software Engineering Intern at JPMorgan Chase 6/2021—8/2021

- Worked as full-stack software engineer on a project to be deployed into production
- JavaScript React / Redux front-end
- Java Spring Boot back-end
- Cassandra database
- Deployment with Jenkins
- Agile development with Jira and Bitbucket

### **Undergraduate Teaching Assistant for CSCE 121** 9/2021—Present

- In charge of leading weekly lab sections
- Hold frequent office hours to assist students with lab exercises and homework
- Help formulate course materials including exam questions
- Grading responsibilities
- CSCE 121 covers object-oriented programming, dynamic memory, debugging, algorithms, and software development

### Code Sensei at Code Ninjas 6/2018—12/2021

- Worked at Code Ninjas The Woodlands and Code Ninjas Magnolia
- Primarily instructive and tutoring work with students aged 7—
  16 in JavaScript, Python, and C#
- Served in a lead role which included advising other locations and training new Senseis
- Developed documentation for JavaScript curriculum used at several locations across the United States
- Designed and implemented a introduction to Python camp

# Eagle Scout 2013—2018

- © College Station, TX
- www.jacksonhagood.com
- github.com/JacksonHagood

# Programming

#### C++

- Experience with OOP, algorithms, abstract data types, and computer systems
- Teaching experience as CSE TA

#### Java

- Experience with OOP, abstract data types, and multi-threading
- **Spring Boot** API development

#### **JavaScript**

- Asynchronous programming, OOP, and Node JS
- React JS / Redux JS
- HTML / CSS

#### **Python**

- Experience with OOP and mathematical modeling (NumPy)
- Flask full stack development
- Code Ninjas camp development

#### **Other Technologies**

- Cassandra
- PostgreSQL
- Haskell
- ARM Assembly
- Lua
- MATLAB
- Git
- Jenkins
- Jira / Bitbucket

# Skills

#### **Electrical Engineering**

- Circuit design and analysis
- Signals and systems
- Verilog
- SPICE and Multisim

#### **Mathematics**

- Cryptography
- Calculus / differential equations
- Linear algebra and applied math
- Discrete math

#### 3D Modeling & CAD

 Blender, Maya, 3DS Max, and AutoCAD

#### **Computer Hardware**